Avenge the fallen.
Avengers: Endgame is a adventure, science fiction,
action film directed by Anthony Russo.
After the devastating events of Avengers: Infinity War, the universe is
in ruins due to the efforts of the Mad Titan, Thanos.
With the help of remaining allies, the Avengers must assemble once more in order to undo Thanos' actions and
restore order to the universe once and for all, no matter what consequences may be in store.
Tony Stark / Iron Man, played by Robert Downey Jr..
Steve Rogers / Captain America, played by Chris Evans.
Bruce Banner / Hulk, played by Mark Ruffalo.
Thor, played by Chris Hemsworth.
Natasha Romanoff / Black Widow, played by Scarlett Johansson.
Clint Barton / Hawkeye, played by Jeremy Renner.
Avengers: Endgame (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack) is the film score for the Marvel
Studios film Avengers: Endgame composed and conducted by Alan Silvestri.
Hollywood Records released the soundtrack album digitally on April 26, 2019,
with the physical formats being released on May 24, 2019.
The film explores themes of superhero, time travel,
space travel, time machine, based on comic.
The tone is thought_provoking.